knowing kind of just kind of playing off
the season. What do you what's it like
knowing you don't really have a ton of
playoffs [clears throat] any
>> um
really just trying to finish strong,
finish out with wins and
you know just keep playing at the end of
the day just make sure we finish strong.
Can't go out there and embarrassing
ourselves or organization on what we
putting ourselves out there. Do you
sense the guys are still bought in and
bringing normal energy?
>> I would say yeah, for the most part. You
know what I'm saying? Everybody in
locker room sales, still talkative. So,
>> what do you use as motivation? Do you
need to use anything as motivation given
where you guys are at?
>> Um,
I wouldn't say anything motivates me
right now. I'm already self motivated,
but I already just pushing myself going
every day. Um, it's not easy being in a
situation like this, but going forward,
I got to make sure my character and just
what I represent about myself and who
I'm representing at the end of the day.
>> Is it hard for you, Jamar, to stay
disciplined in your game when you know
that games aren't don't determine any
standings don't determine playoffs? It's
more important to like stay within what
you're trying to do.
uh
>> freelancing. You're not like just
freelancing out there. You're trying to
stay within the game plan.
>> I mean, yeah, for the most part. I mean,
majority of the time we we we play like
that. I think we don't always like
freelance. I think unless it's like
offscript scramble drill, you know what
I'm saying? That's the only time we we
might have those opportunities. But
other than that, everything's pretty
much on script.
>> When you watch the film from the
Baltimore game, what what stood out
after reviewing it?
Uh
there just a lot of missed opportunities
we had. You know what I'm saying? To
make the game stay alive for ourselves
just to have ourselves in a better
position for the fourth quarter.
>> Are you looking forward to the 80 degree
81 degree kickoff temp or does it
matter?
>> Uh
really don't matter. I'm just making
sure I'm staying hydrated at the end of
the day. That's the biggest thing.
cuz like have you ever been on a team
that had a losing record at any level?
>> Um, no. This is my first time. I mean,
past couple years, I guess, but other
than that,
>> you know, you guys didn't make playoffs,
but you got to win the record.
>> Yeah. But
>> you guys are nine and eight past years.
>> You felt like losing.
>> You don't make the playoffs. You know
what I'm saying?
>> This the [clears throat] longest score.
>> Um, probably I don't know how long it's
been. I can't remember.
>> Yeah, I don't remember either.
>> Is that Is that a It's going to be a
long stretch.
>> Oh, that it was a long time. Yeah.
>> Steelers here.
>> Long long time ago.
>> Well, you get a lot of attention in the
red zone.
>> Yeah. I mean, still missed opportunities
sometimes. You know what I'm saying? But
still still happens.
>> Feel like you do.
Uh, I think I'm always due for a
touchdown. Leave me think I'm supposed
to score every game. What do you think?
[laughter]
>> For you and the other typical starters,
why is it important in your mind for you
guys to still play out the last three
games of the season even though the
goals that you set are not on the table
anymore?
>> Um,
I mean, at the end of the day is is what
we do for a living. You know what I'm
saying? just cuz we don't want to
finish. I don't really see like why
that's such a big thing. You know what
I'm saying? At the end of the day, it's
still our job. We still got to come to
work, do the same thing every day. It
don't matter like if we don't want to go
out there now. We still got to finish
it. You know what I'm saying? So, it's
all up to that's really
a personal thing on somebody if they
don't want to do that. So, at the end of
the day, everybody should be on the same
page trying to play for one another. We
all putting our line on the body for
everybody at the end of the day. So,
>> have you started to reflect at all on
this season? I know you're still in it,
but have you have you reflected at all?
And if so, how would you sum up what
this year has been?
>> Um, no. I haven't yet really sat there
and reflected on it or just accepted
what happened this year. No, not yet.
I'm probably going to wait for the
season to end to really get into that.
>> This season of disappointments, is there
one or two things that stand out to you
as things you'll remember fondly? that
you've accomplished or the team's
accomplished offense, anything
>> talking about from this year?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm not saying, but Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Are those the kind of things, like James
was saying, you'll look back on at the
end of the year and reflect on or you
can appreciate them now?
>> No. Yeah. 100%. I would I would say so.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? It it'll
build a lot of emotions for sure.
>> What do you want to accomplish over
these next three games as a team?
Obviously, you're building now for 26.
What what can you what can y'all do over
the next three games that puts y'all in
a decent position to start next year the
way y'all want to?
>> Um I don't know. I I don't really know
how to answer a question like that. You
know what I'm saying? I mean,
the only thing we could do is prepare
and to put put to put ourselves in a
best situation for game time at the end
of the day. I mean, we can't really
reflect on what's going to happen next
year because that's out of our control.
Nobody knows what's going to happen in
the future. So, we just got to prepare
for the game that's coming up and that's
how we going to finish. Think of it this
way. You guys ended last year five in a
row. Do you feel like that had any kind
of impact that you went into this year
because you ended the year as well as
you could have without making the
playoffs?
>> No. No.
>> No. No. I didn't we didn't make the
playoffs. I was just itching to play
football again. So, no.
>> How do you feel about the front office
in this coaching staff?
>> Um, I feel great about him at the end of
the day. I I don't have no problems with
nobody. Um, I got a great bond with the
staff. Um, my receiver coach, Zack,
pitch. I mean, from O line to tight
ends, you know what I'm saying? We all
communicate with everybody. So, I I like
the staff.
>> You were here the moment you got here.
Yeah. Go to the Super Bowl and back
toback AFC Championship games. The past
three years obviously haven't
>> gone that way.
>> Is there a reason why, whether it's
coaching players, like any anything like
that that that stands out to you?
cuz you're still here. Joe's here. T's
here.
>> I think it's just stay in the NFL, man.
I think it's not easy. At the end of the
day, I don't think it's pretty easy. So,
um, the more better we get, the more
people going to adapt to what we did
last year and try to figure out how to
stop it. And that's what it is. It's the
NFL. We got to get used to people
adapting to us. We got to adjust
sometimes and that's what it's going to
be.
>> Do you feel like y'all have done a good
enough job that over the course of the
year?
>> Uh, yeah. I think we had great
opportunities, great game plans to to to
showcase what we could beat and how we
can't be stopped. You know, we showed it
plenty of times. Um, but it don't always
end out the best way for us.
>> Do you look at the receiving [snorts]
lead?
>> I haven't past two weeks. Not really.
Not lately.
>> Any reason why?
>> Um,
I just ain't been paying attention to
it. What about it?
>> Kind of uh I think it close to the
receptions. A couple receptions off
maybe.
>> My dad was telling me something after
the game about someh some record. I
don't know what he was talking about.
>> I don't know what he's talking about.
[laughter] I don't know what he's
talking about. I really don't.
>> I mean, take your pick. I mean, because
you got all these records about fastest,
you know.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You got a school.
Is there is there more I'm about to
break or something? I mean, I don't know
what's what's right. I don't know what's
going on until y'all tell me or the
Bengals post me and other than that, I
don't really keep up with it.
>> I mean, it's something every
>> Well, that mean that means I'm I'm
providing that means I'm giving off good
good uh good stats, right?
>> Doing something.
>> Absolutely.
I mean it's like uh
you know you're kind of going headtohead
with for a couple different categories.
>> He's been he's been incredible this
year.
>> Yeah. [snorts]
>> Past two years.
>> Do you watch Thursday night football?
He's playing tonight.
>> He is. Thanks for telling me. I just
found out. Yeah. Thanks for telling me.
[laughter]
What time?
>> What time? 8.
>> Yeah. I mean, this is getting really
this is getting really this is probably
probably wouldn't interest you, but I
mean, uh, you were for you were the one
second on the alltime list for most
yards per game and now like Pa just went
by you by about a yard.
>> I can I can see that.
>> Yeah,
>> he made some unbelievable catches.
>> You know what I'm saying? So,
>> what do you like about how much how much
have you seen his game? Um,
really the biggest thing when I turn on
this tape is he make contested catches.
Like if that's that's that's one really
big thing, you know what I'm saying? I
see him do all the time. Like and it's
very consistent.
>> When you watch tonight, you watch
tonight.
>> Say it again.
>> I said you watch tonight, huh?
>> Your accent, Jeff. [snorts]
>> You said I watched tonight.
>> I said you will watch tonight.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. See, your accent
right there. It was like you watched
like you was telling me. It was a lot.
It was a lot. It's all right, Jeeoff. I
still love you, brother.
>> I don't want to tell you anything.
[laughter]
>> I would only ask
>> when when you are watching a game on TV
like that between, you know, two random
teams, whoever it might be, how do you
watch the game? Like, like what are you
paying attention? Like, are you watching
just for enjoyment or
>> Well, first let me know who's playing
against the Rams playing who?
>> The Seahawks.
Um, so right basically I'm going to be
watching like the receivers and probably
just how the defense playing the
receivers. You know what I'm saying? So
that's the biggest thing. You know what
I'm saying? Cuz all the receivers get
played differently. Like
>> you you almost do watch it from like a
film.
>> Of course. Yeah. That's the only way I
would, you know, that's the only way you
get better at the game. You know what
I'm saying? Cuz Jen is a deep threat,
but Puka is like pretty much all over
the field. You know what I'm saying? So
it's it's a two different type of
receivers at the end of the day.
>> Can you watch a game from just an
enjoyment standpoint? like and not look
at the
>> No, if I'm watching football, I'm going
to dissect it like down. So, that's why
I don't like watching it that much cuz
my brain start thinking too hard.
>> Is that enjoyable for you?
>> Say it again.
>> Not when I don't like what's going to
happen. Like, if I don't like to play
that play out, I get pissed off. I mean,
but I can't control it.
>> Does it matter who wins, loses? Do you
just look at how they play?
>> Yeah, I just watching how they play,
learning, and seeing what DBs is and
doing what? Jamar, do you feel like this
season in some ways when you work so
hard, does it feel like a waste or does
it feel like part of your story and part
of your journey as well?
>> Uh, at the end of the day, it's still
part of my journey. You know what I'm
saying? I'm big building a legacy for
myself and my kids. Um, and at the end
of the day, they going to watch this and
go back and see how I am and see how
hard I worked and, you know, they
[clears throat] might go off that.
>> Does No, we don't know if I think Minko
is going to play. I think he's week to
week. How does your defense change if
Minko's not out there? Obviously, a guy
that y'all know really well.
>> Um, they're pretty much a zone team. you
know, it's it's a little different from
what we used to know Minka in. Um,
but you know, it's it'll be and now I
think he plays a lot of nickel there.
You know what I'm saying? So, he moves
around a little more. So, I I wouldn't I
can't really have a full answer on that.
>> When you when you see a defense that's
got so many veterans, like just any
opponent, what is that like preparing
for a team when you know they've got a
lot of capable vets on the other side of
the ball who've been in the league a
long time and can make things difficult
for you? Um, really just
when you playing teams like that, it's
really just trying to get yourselves out
of the the third and longs. You know
what I'm saying? You want to put
yourselves in the first and 10, second
and shorts, you know what I'm saying?
Um, and you want to stay in those ranges
and that's and that's the hardest part
about that when you're playing against
the guys that that know concept concepts
really good.
>> Zach has talked a lot about uh not Zach,
Joe talked a lot about the coaching
staff and Zack last couple of weeks.
What do you appreciate most about Zack
Taylor and kind of what what he does for
you as a head coach?
>> Uh, I would say he's a a player's coach
at the end of the day. You know what I'm
saying? He bonds with us. Um, looks out
for us, make sure we're good at the end
of the day. Um, not afraid to talk to us
if anything. Um, so I say he's a helping
hand for that for sure.
>> Do you ever think that the coaching
staff, front office, whoever could be
tougher on the team collectively,
individually, what have you?
>> Can it happen? Yes.
>> Should they should they be at times?
>> I don't I'm not telling them what to do.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> It seems like with Joe, with several
other players we've talked to in the
locker room, they are very loyal to the
front office ownership coaching staff.
Why do you think that is?
>> Um, probably because they
showed them love when they got here
since rookies. You know what I'm saying?
The bond's been real since since they
were rookies. Um, and over time, you
know, you just keep building on the
relationship and, you know, you still
have one.
>> Are you confident that you guys can get
back to those heights and beyond?
Obviously, you want to reach the
ultimate goal that you did in your first
two years. And, and if so, what gives
you that confidence?
>> Uh, I mean, yeah, obviously, man, we got
best duo and quarterback. You know what
I'm saying? We've been every year I feel
like we've been getting better in the
running game and proceeding in
expectation we've been trying to do from
last year. So, it's been getting better
every year. Um, just got to we just got
to find that piece. Whatever piece we
got to find, we got to find it, add it
in, make sure it fits us well and
compliments us well for for game time.
>> When you look at the success from early
in your career, the Super Bowl and the
separate AFC Championship game, then
contrast that with now three straight
years of missing the playoffs. Has that
changed the way that you look at this
league or this team or yourself or your
career? Has it changed your perspective
at all?
>> No. I mean, in offseason, I still work
as hard as I do. You know what I'm
saying? I can't at the end of the day, I
can only control what I can control and
that's coming in me and being that's
coming in me being the best player and
helping others around me be better. Um,
and that's all I can do. Provide for the
team, produce when it's time for me to
produce.
>> Jamar, going off that a little bit. Uh,
Jeeoff, I'm sorry.
>> Go ahead. Sorry, bud. Um, going off that
a little bit, I was wondering if um, you
know, you've stepped into a more
prominent leadership role this year. I
think you've relished that. Does,
does does leading for like during this
3-week period where you guys would be
out of playoff contention. Does that
look or feel different? Do do you have
to
step up even more, change the way you
lead, or is it stay the same?
Oh, that's a good question. Um,
I would say stay the same, but you know,
has still have urgency at the end of the
day. That's the biggest thing. Um,
just because we don't we don't have
anything in the future this year just
doesn't mean we can't have urgency with
the next three games and practicing and
attacking it the same way and preparing
the same way so we can produce during
game time.
>> Are there older receivers you talked to
uh that maybe might be in a similar spot
where they've been really great on some
not great teams and how they balance
that over there? Is that is that you
know have you picked anyone's brains
about that?
>> I don't I don't do no stuff like that if
I'm being honest. No.
>> Consider like is that would that be
beneficial for you or No.
>> Uh no. I don't think so. I mean you
going to tell me to go work hard in the
offseason too. You know what I'm saying?
>> Did you talk to Chad the other day when
he was here?
>> Uhuh. No.
>> I mean during the game that was it but
that was pretty much it. Yeah.
>> So what Jeff?
>> I'm sorry the guy [laughter] was The guy
from Seattle's having hell of a year,
too.
>> Yes.
>> You looked at his numbers.
>> He's um he's like, 1500 right now. I
seen something like that.
>> What's he see? [clears throat]
>> Yeah. I I'm uh I'm not understanding how
he's getting behind these safeties every
play. Um
but he runs from what I'm seeing from
the clips that I do see, he runs good
routes. You know what I'm saying? He
makes separation, runs good routes, gets
out of his breaks pretty good. He makes
contested catches, too. That's a big
thing, you know what I'm saying? With
him, him him and Puka this year. And,
you know what I'm saying? You look at
Puka from the past two years, you know
what I'm saying? He's always been making
contested catches. And that's, you know,
that's where the big chunks come from.
>> Is it too late to catch those two guys?
>> Um, probably JS. Yeah. I don't know what
Puka is. Puka's at, but 1500, you get
400 yards in one week.
>> You will not be getting the ball next
week. 100% sure.
>> I just wonder what your Oh, I'm sorry,
Bennett. I just want to get this one in
here. the uh were you surprised on
Sunday when you looked at the stat sheet
and you were 10 for 132?
>> Um
>> seemed like you were frustrated all game
it seemed like maybe you were having a
60 yard game or something.
>> Um
>> I didn't know what I had until the end
of the game. I don't really know what I
have until the end of the game. Did it
>> surprise you that you had 130?
>> Yeah, I wasn't expecting 130. It should
have been way more. We had a lot of
missed opportunities at the end of the
day. I think that's what pissed me off
the most.
it. You know, you always believe you're
one of the best receivers in the league.
Numbers haven't been there like they
were in previous years. How tough is it
when you know you're that good, but
maybe won't get the same accolades like
that last year like Puka and JSN seem to
be the allp pro guys. Uh how tough is
that knowing how good you are, but it's
not always going to be reflected in the
accolades for personally as well.
>> Um I know I know I'm one of the best out
there, if not one of the best the best
because we can look at the defense and
look at the structure of the defense and
and tell where everybody looking to on
defense. So that right there is a lot
for me talking. I don't have to show my
accolades or nothing for it. [snorts]
>> Is that something you hope people when
you're done at the end of your career
that they like with Calvin Johnson it
was similar? Is that something they hope
they remember?
>> Exactly. Exactly how it's going to be.
Yeah.
>> Thanks Jamar. Thanks.
>> Thank you Jamar. [clears throat]